<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Services on Aerele Technologies</title>
    <link>/services/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Services on Aerele Technologies</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/services/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Enterprise Portals</title>
      <link>/services/enterprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/enterprise/</guid>
      <description>Turn to us to get your business integrated into the connected software ecosystem.We do design, develop,maintain and support software solutions for enterprises with a whole lot of flexibility of engagement models and scopes. We not only get legacy systems migrated to newer platforms but also enrich it with fresh features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prototyping</title>
      <link>/services/prototyping/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/prototyping/</guid>
      <description>We build incremental prototypes to make any complex functionality ideas or applications simple helping our customers to envision it.With Conceptual Designs, Personas User Task Flows,Site Maps, Mood Boards, Adaptive Layouts and a few more, We will assay to get you and your ideas covered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manufacturing Applications</title>
      <link>/services/manufacturing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/manufacturing/</guid>
      <description>Hailing from the Manchester of South India surrounded by manufacturing firms,you can expect the wealth of technical and business expertise combo in our solutions to any of your diverse and complex business needs. You can trust that we&amp;rsquo;ll do it right the first time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technology Consulting</title>
      <link>/services/consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/consulting/</guid>
      <description>Our dedicated efforts in the entire cycle of software application development with flexible delivery models and effective project management will let you focus on your business strengths, while we cover the technological advancements that are needed to sustain, stay upto the market standards and grow in this digital era.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DevOps Integrations</title>
      <link>/services/devops/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/devops/</guid>
      <description>Techies, you shall innovate faster more reliably while we optimize your capabilities in terms of infrasctructure automation, continous integration and continous delivery.Behind the scenes, it boosts your developement speed, relaiability and efficiency by embracing an automated and agile way of working.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Requirements Engineering</title>
      <link>/services/requirements_engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/requirements_engineering/</guid>
      <description>We elicit and validate your requirements throughly right from scratch to define the scope and context of the projects. We are determined to ensure all the use cases to be complete, correct, feasible, concise,prioritized, unambiguous and verifiable.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>